https://islanddelights.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Welcome to the web site (the “Site”) of Island Delights, Inc. (“Island Delights, Inc.”, “IDI”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how information is collected from our users (“you”, ”your”) when you use this online website, mobile website, application, digital service, or any related products, services, sites, social media, features or functionality (each a “Service”, collectively the “Services”) and how IDI uses, shares and manages your information and data, including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”). By using any of the Services, you consent to the collection, use, processing, and sharing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Our Collection and Use of Personal Information and Non-Personal Information: IDI does not require visitors to submit personal information to visit our Websites. IDI only collects personal information from visitors to our Websites on a voluntary basis. Visitors may be required to submit personal information to register for specific promotions or participate in certain online programs, surveys, newsletters or other transactions or activities; such submission of personal information, however, is deemed to be voluntary. On a particular IDI registration page, we may request personal information such as, without limitation, the visitor’s date of birth, gender, e-mail address, telephone number, and/or other contact and demographic information. Information submitted is considered voluntary and public information, and IDI reserves the right to use that information in on-line and off-line marketing materials. IDI reserves the right to limit participation in particular programs or promotions based on eligibility factors, including age. IDI does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13 years of age.
IDI may collect non-personal information from online visitors, such as the visitor’s browser type, operating system and domain name. The non-personal information we collect enables us to track the total number of visitors to each of our sites in an aggregate form, and is used by IDI to improve and update our Websites, products and services. IDI uses information submitted by visitors as described at the time information is collected, and to keep track of visitors’ participation in our promotions and programs, to respond to comments or questions, to notify a visitor if he or she is the potential winner of a promotion, to send special messages regarding our Websites, products, programs or promotions, to provide visitors with access to special areas or features of our Website(s), and for internal and business purposes.
Our Disclosure of Collected Personal Information and Non-Personal Information: IDI may share personal information and non-personal information with any entity within our corporate family, existing now or in the future, including business entities with whom we merge or acquire. Except as otherwise permitted in this Privacy Policy, IDI does not share personal information or non-personal information about a visitor to third parties for those third parties’ marketing purposes without the explicit consent of the visitor.
IDI may disclose personal information to comply with a subpoena, applicable law or process, if IDI believes it is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or to protect our company or the privacy or safety of visitors to our Websites. IDI may hire trusted companies to help us with our Websites, programs and promotions, and those companies may have limited access to personal information for the sole purpose of performing their services, subject to confidentiality obligations.
Non-personal information may be shared with third parties at the discretion of IDI. Social Media Platforms and Other Websites Our Websites may contain links to social media platforms, and you may be given the choice of connecting to one or more social media platforms from our Websites and/or integrating your social media experience with a program or promotion on our Websites. If you choose to do so, depending on your social media privacy settings, the personal information that you post, transmit or otherwise make available on the social media platform may be viewed and/or used by others. IDI does not control and is not responsible for any use of your personal information by or through the social media platform. By linking to a social media platform, you assume the risk that the personal information you provide on that platform may be viewed and/or used by third parties for any purposes.
Security: IDI uses appropriate industry standard means, including technical safeguards, to protect any sensitive information that might be submitted on our Websites. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information and non-personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from our Websites. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. We will not be liable for damages related to any unlawful access to your information unless said access is due to our gross negligence or intentional act. IDI does not tolerate spam. To report IDI-related spam or spoof e-mails to IDI, please forward the e-mail to sales@islanddelights.com.
How to Modify Personal Information or Remove Your Personal Information from Our Records:If you have opted to participate in a IDI promotion or program and/or to receive information from us, and have provided IDI certain personal information, you may modify your personal information or remove yourself from our records by calling or e-mailing us your request at:
Island Delights, Inc.1.866.887.4100sales@islanddelights.com
General TermsThis Privacy Policy may be amended by IDI at any time by updating this posting. Please check back periodically to review the Privacy Policy. All amended terms are automatically effective when posted. If you have questions or comments about the Website or this Privacy Policy, please contact IDI at 1.866.887.4100 on weekdays between 9:00 a.m. and 5:00 p.m. EST.
Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this policy addresses only the use and disclosure of information Island collect from you. If you disclose your information to others on our Websites or other websites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to the use or disclosure of the information you disclose. Island does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to review privacy policies and ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.
The information in our Websites is provided without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied, including all warranties on merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, title or non-infringement of third-party rights, nor the accuracy or completeness or timeline of any information herein. The foregoing applies to any information in any of our Websites hyperlinked to this website. The material could contain inaccuracies or be outdated. In no event will Island be liable to any person for any damage of any kind for use of or reliance upon these materials, including any omissions in any materials.
This Privacy Policy was last revised in October 14, 2019. All rights reserved.
